Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series LXXIV. WAGES
  - Sub-Series 408-295. Wages
    - Union Terminal Railway, St. Joseph, Missouri. St. Joseph Belt Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 572, Folder 15)
    - Union Terminal Railway, St. Joseph, Missouri. St. Joseph Belt Railway. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 572, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 408-296. Wages
    - Texas Mexican Railway. General, 1938-1956 (Box 572, Folder 17)
    - Texas Mexican Railway. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 572, Folder 18)
    - Texas Mexican Railway. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 572, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 408-300. Wages
    - Pacific and Atlantic Shipping Association, Inc. General, 1943-1951 (Box 572, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 408-301. Wages
    - New York and Long Branch Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 572, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 408-304. Wages
    - Trans-Continental Freight Bureau North. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 572, Folder 22)
    - Trans-Continental Freight Bureau South. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 572, Folder 23)
    - Trans-Continental Freight Bureau North. Trans-Continental Freight Bureau South. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 572, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 408-305. Wages
    - Detroit, Toledo and Ironton Railroad. General, 1941-1950 (Box 572, Folder 25)
      1941-March 1950.
    - Detroit, Toledo and Ironton Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 572, Folder 26)
    - Detroit, Toledo and Ironton Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 572, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 408-307. Wages
    - Los Angeles Union Passenger Terminal. General, 1941-1953 (Box 572, Folder 28)
    - Los Angeles Union Passenger Terminal. Agreements. Clerks, Red Caps. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 572, Folder 29)
    - Los Angeles Union Passenger Terminal. Agreements. Clerks, Red Caps. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 572, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 408-308. Wages
    - Union Freight Railroad, Boston, Massachusetts. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 572, Folder 31)
    - Union Freight Railroad, Boston, Massachusetts. General., 1947-1951 (Box 572, Folder 32)
    - Union Freight Railroad, Boston, Massachusetts. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 572, Folder 33)
    - Union Freight Railroad, Boston, Massachusetts. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 572, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 408-309. Wages
    - Meridian Terminal Company. General, 1932-1958 (Box 572, Folder 35)
    - Meridian Terminal Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement. Mediation Case No. A-7067, 1963-1965 (Box 572, Folder 36)
    - Meridian Terminal Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 572, Folder 37)
    - Meridian Terminal Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 572, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 408-310. Wages
    - Railroad Perishable Inspection Agency. General, 1947-1953 (Box 572, Folder 39)
    - Railroad Perishable Inspection Agency. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 572, Folder 40)
    - Railroad Perishable Inspection Agency. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 572, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 408-313. Wages
    - Rock Island Frisco Terminal Railway. General, 1945-1953 (Box 572, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 408-314. Wages
    - Chicago, North Shore, and Milwaukee Railway. General, 1947-1955 (Box 572, Folder 43)
    - Chicago, North Shore, and Milwaukee Railway. 1956 Wage Movement. 1957 Wage Increase Request. Mediation Cases Nos. A-5405 and A-5601, 1956-1957 (Box 572, Folder 44)
    - Chicago, North Shore, and Milwaukee Railway. Mediation Case No. A-5148, 1955-1956 (Box 572, Folder 45)
    - Chicago, North Shore, and Milwaukee Railway. Mediation Cases Nos. A-3955 and A-4030, 1950-1953 (Box 572, Folder 46)
    - Chicago, North Shore, and Milwaukee Railway. Mediation Case No. A-4280, 1952-1953 (Box 572, Folder 47)
    - Chicago, North Shore, and Milwaukee Railway. Mediation Case No. A-3608, 1949-1951 (Box 572, Folder 48)
    - Chicago, North Shore, and Milwaukee Railway. Mediation Case No. A-3214, 1949-1951 (Box 572, Folder 49)
    - Chicago, North Shore, and Milwaukee Railway. Bozell and Jacobs Advertising, Inc. Press Clippings, 1948 (Box 572, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 408-315. Wages
    - Rutherford Service Company. General, 1948 (Box 572, Folder 51)
    - Rutherford Service Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 572, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 408-316. Wages
    - Stock Yards District Agency. Mediation Case No. A-4807, 1955-1956 (Box 573, Folder 1)
    - Stock Yards District Agency. 40-Hour Week, 1948-1953 (Box 573, Folder 2)
    - Stock Yards District Agency. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 573, Folder 3)
    - Stock Yards District Agency. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 573, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 408-317. Wages
    - North Pacific Coast Freight Bureau. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 573, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 408-319. Wages
    - Chattanooga Station Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement. Mediation Case No. A-7067, 1963-1965 (Box 573, Folder 6)
    - Chattanooga Station Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 573, Folder 7)
    - Chattanooga Station Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 573, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 408-320. Wages
    - Durham Union Station Company. General, 1932-1954 (Box 573, Folder 9)
    - Durham Union Station Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement. Mediation Case No. A-7067, 1963-1965 (Box 573, Folder 10)
    - Durham Union Station Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 573, Folder 11)
    - Durham Union Station Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 573, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 408-321. Wages
    - Columbia Union Station Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement. Mediation Case No. A-7067, 1963-1965 (Box 573, Folder 13)
    - Columbia Union Station Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 573, Folder 14)
    - Columbia Union Station Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 573, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 408-322. Wages
    - Western Warehousing Company. General, 1950-1955 (Box 573, Folder 16)
    - Western Warehousing Company. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 573, Folder 17)
    - Western Warehousing Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 573, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 408-323. Wages
    - Lackawanna and Wyoming Valley Railroad Company. 1955 Wage Movement. 1956 Wage Movement, 1955-1957 (Box 573, Folder 19)
    - Lackawanna and Wyoming Valley Railroad Company. Mediation Case No. A-4035, 1950-1955 (Box 573, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 408-326. Wages
    - New York, Susquehanna, and Western Railroad. General, 1938-1953 (Box 573, Folder 21)
    - New York, Susquehanna, and Western Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 573, Folder 22)
    - New York, Susquehanna, and Western Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 573, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 408-329. Wages
    - Union Motor Coach Terminal Company, Chicago, Illinois. General, 1952-1953 (Box 573, Folder 24)
    - Union Motor Coach Terminal Company, Chicago, Illinois. General, 1941-1951 (Box 573, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 408-330. Wages
    - Overland Terminal Warehouse Company, Los Angeles, California. General, 1941-1953 (Box 573, Folder 26)
    - Overland Terminal Warehouse Company, Los Angeles, California. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1964 (Box 573, Folder 27)
    - Overland Terminal Warehouse Company, Los Angeles, California. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 573, Folder 28)
    - Overland Terminal Warehouse Company, Los Angeles, California. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 573, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 408-333. Wages
    - Atlanta and West Point Railroad. Western Railway of Alabama. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 573, Folder 30)
    - Atlanta and West Point Railroad. Western Railway of Alabama. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 573, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 408-334. Wages
    - Spokane International Railroad Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 573, Folder 32)
    - Spokane International Railroad Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 573, Folder 33)
    - Spokane International Railroad Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 573, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 408-335. Wages
    - New Orleans and Lower Coast Railroad. General, 1950-1951 (Box 573, Folder 35)
      February 1950-51.
    - New Orleans and Lower Coast Railroad. General, 1942-1950 (Box 573, Folder 36)
      1942-February 1950.
  - Sub-Series 408-336. Wages
    - Detroit and Cleveland Navigation Company. General, 1945-1951 (Box 573, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 408-338. Wages
    - National Trailways Bus Depot, Chicago, Illinois. General, 1941-1955 (Box 573, Folder 38)
    - National Trailways Bus Depot, Chicago, Illinois. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 573, Folder 39)
    - National Trailways Bus Depot, Chicago, Illinois. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 573, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 408-339. Wages
    - Fort Dodge, Des Moines and Southern Railway Company. General, 1954-1957 (Box 573, Folder 41)
    - Fort Dodge, Des Moines and Southern Railway Company. General, 1941-1953 (Box 573, Folder 42)
    - Fort Dodge, Des Moines and Southern Railway Company. Agreements. Clerical, Office Station and Storehouse Employees; Station Agents. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 573, Folder 43)
    - Fort Dodge, Des Moines and Southern Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 573, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 408-340. Wages
    - Augusta Union Station, Augusta, Georgia. General, 1941-1955 (Box 573, Folder 45)
    - Augusta Union Station, Augusta, Georgia. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 573, Folder 46)
    - Augusta Union Station, Augusta, Georgia. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 573, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 408-341. Wages
    - Parmalee Transportation Company. General, 1942-1955 (Box 573, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 408-343. Wages
    - Ashley, Drew and Northern Railway. General, 1942-1953 (Box 573, Folder 49)
    - Ashley, Drew and Northern Railway. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 574, Folder 1)
    - Ashley, Drew and Northern Railway. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 574, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 408-344. Wages
    - Fruit Growers Express Company. General, 1942-1950 (Box 574, Folder 3)
    - Fruit Growers Express Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 574, Folder 4)
    - Fruit Growers Express Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 574, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 408-345. Wages
    - Fonda, Johnstown and Gloversville Railroad. General, 1954-1955 (Box 574, Folder 6)
    - Fonda, Johnstown and Gloversville Railroad. General, 1942-1953 (Box 574, Folder 7)
    - Fonda, Johnstown and Gloversville Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 574, Folder 8)
    - Fonda, Johnstown and Gloversville Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 574, Folder 9)
    - Fonda, Johnstown and Gloversville Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 574, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 408-346. Wages
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line. General, 1950-1956 (Box 574, Folder 11)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 574, Folder 12)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 574, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 408-347. Wages
    - Norfolk Terminal Railway, Norfolk, Virginia. General, 1954 (Box 574, Folder 14)
    - Norfolk Terminal Railway, Norfolk, Virginia. General, 1943-1953 (Box 574, Folder 15)
    - Norfolk Terminal Railway, Norfolk, Virginia. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 574, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 408-349. Wages
    - Denver Union Stock Yards Company. General, 1955-1956 (Box 574, Folder 17)
    - Denver Union Stock Yards Company. General, 1942-1954 (Box 574, Folder 18)
    - Denver Union Stock Yards Company. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1960 (Box 574, Folder 19)
    - Denver Union Stock Yards Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 574, Folder 20)
    - Denver Union Stock Yards Company. 40-Hour Week, 1948-1951 (Box 574, Folder 21)
    - Denver Union Stock Yards Company. Mediation Case No. A-3674, 1950-1953 (Box 574, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 408-350. Wages
    - Lake Terminal Railroad Company. General, 1945-1952 (Box 574, Folder 23)
    - Lake Terminal Railroad Company. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 574, Folder 24)
    - Lake Terminal Railroad Company. Mediation Case No. A-5194, 1956 (Box 574, Folder 25)
    - Lake Terminal Railroad Company. Mediation Case No. A-4053, 1952-1955 (Box 574, Folder 26)
    - Lake Terminal Railroad Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 574, Folder 27)
    - Lake Terminal Railroad Company. Mediation Case No. A-4170, 1953 (Box 574, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 408-351. Wages
    - Georgia and Florida Railroad. General, 1935-1955 (Box 574, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 408-352. Wages
    - Lehigh and Hudson River Railway Company. General, 1942-1954 (Box 574, Folder 30)
    - Lehigh and Hudson River Railway Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 574, Folder 31)
    - Lehigh and Hudson River Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 574, Folder 32)
    - Lehigh and Hudson River Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 574, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 408-353. Wages
    - Davenport, Rock Island and Northwestern Railroad. General, 1954-1955 (Box 574, Folder 34)
    - Davenport, Rock Island and Northwestern Railroad. General, 1938-1953 (Box 574, Folder 35)
    - Davenport, Rock Island and Northwestern Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 574, Folder 36)
    - Davenport, Rock Island and Northwestern Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 574, Folder 37)
    - Davenport, Rock Island and Northwestern Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 574, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 408-354. Wages
    - Spokane Union Station, Spokane, Washington. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 574, Folder 39)
    - Spokane Union Station, Spokane, Washington. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 574, Folder 40)
    - Spokane Union Station, Spokane, Washington. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 574, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 408-355. Wages
    - East Portland Freight Terminal, Portland, Oregon. General, 1937-1953 (Box 575, Folder 1)
    - East Portland Freight Terminal, Portland, Oregon. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 575, Folder 2)
    - East Portland Freight Terminal, Portland, Oregon. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 575, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 408-356. Wages
    - Cleveland Union Terminals Company, Cleveland, Ohio. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 575, Folder 4)
    - Cleveland Union Terminals Company, Cleveland, Ohio. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 575, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 408-358. Wages
    - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. New York Terminals. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 575, Folder 6)
    - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. New York Terminals. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 575, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 408-359. Wages
    - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. Chicago Terminal Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 575, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 408-360. Wages
    - Pittsburgh Joint Stock Yards Company. General, 1954 (Box 575, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh Joint Stock Yards Company. General, 1940-1953 (Box 575, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh Joint Stock Yards Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 575, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh Joint Stock Yards Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 575, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 408-361. Wages
    - Terminal Storage Company of Washington, D.C. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 575, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 408-362. Wages
    - Tampa Union Station, Tampa, Florida. General, 1945-1954 (Box 575, Folder 14)
    - Tampa Union Station, Tampa, Florida. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 575, Folder 15)
    - Tampa Union Station, Tampa, Florida. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 575, Folder 16)
    - Tampa Union Station, Tampa, Florida. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 575, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 408-363. Wages
    - Hannibal Union Depot, Hannibal, Missouri. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 575, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 408-365. Wages
    - Pittsburgh, Chartiers and Youghiogheny Railway Company. General, 1943-1951 (Box 575, Folder 19)
    - Pittsburgh, Chartiers and Youghiogheny Railway Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 575, Folder 20)
    - Pittsburgh, Chartiers and Youghiogheny Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 575, Folder 21)
    - Pittsburgh, Chartiers and Youghiogheny Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 575, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 408-366. Wages
    - Akron Union Passenger Depot Company, Akron, Ohio. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 575, Folder 23)
    - Akron Union Passenger Depot Company, Akron, Ohio. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 575, Folder 24)
    - Akron Union Passenger Depot Company, Akron, Ohio. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 575, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 408-367. Wages
    - Santa Fe Tie and Lumber Preserving Company. General, 1949-1955 (Box 575, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 408-368. Wages
    - Sioux City Terminal Railway Company, Sioux City, Iowa. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 575, Folder 27)
    - Sioux City Terminal Railway Company, Sioux City, Iowa. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 575, Folder 28)
    - Sioux City Terminal Railway Company, Sioux City, Iowa. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 575, Folder 29)
    - Sioux City Terminal Railway Company, Sioux City, Iowa. General, 1944-1951 (Box 575, Folder 30)
    - 408-369. Wages (Box 575, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series Ogden Union Stock Yards Company, Ogden, Utah. General, 1942-1954
    - Ogden Union Stock Yards Company, Ogden, Utah. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement. Mediation Case No. A-7465, 1963-1965 (Box 575, Folder 32)
    - Ogden Union Stock Yards Company, Ogden, Utah. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1960 (Box 575, Folder 33)
    - Ogden Union Stock Yards Company, Ogden, Utah. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 575, Folder 34)
    - Ogden Union Stock Yards Company, Ogden, Utah. 40-Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 575, Folder 35)
    - Ogden Union Stock Yards Company, Ogden, Utah. Mediation Case No. A-3674, 1951-1953 (Box 575, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 408-370. Wages
    - Wharton and Northern Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 575, Folder 37)
    - Wharton and Northern Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 575, Folder 38)
    - Wharton and Northern Railroad. General, 1942-1944 (Box 575, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 408-372. Wages
    - Missouri-Illinois Railroad Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 575, Folder 40)
    - Missouri-Illinois Railroad Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 575, Folder 41)
    - Missouri-Illinois Railroad Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 575, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 408-373. Wages
    - Salt Lake City Union Depot and Railway Company, Salt Lake City, Utah. General, 1932-1953 (Box 575, Folder 43)
    - Salt Lake City Union Depot and Railway Company, Salt Lake City, Utah. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 575, Folder 44)
    - Salt Lake City Union Depot and Railway Company, Salt Lake City, Utah. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 575, Folder 45)
    - Salt Lake City Union Depot and Railway Company, Salt Lake City, Utah. Mediation Case No. A-2055, 1945 (Box 575, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 408-374. Wages
    - Fred Harvey Service, Inc. General, 1947-1955 (Box 575, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 408-375. Wages
    - New York Central Building Corporation. General, 1943-1955 (Box 575, Folder 48)
    - New York Central Building Corporation. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 575, Folder 49)
    - New York Central Building Corporation. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 575, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 408-376. Wages
    - J.P. Carey and Company. General, 1946-1955 (Box 575, Folder 51)
    - J.P. Carey and Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 575, Folder 52)
    - J.P. Carey and Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 575, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 408-378. Wages
    - Pacific Motor Trucking Company. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 575, Folder 54)
    - Pacific Motor Trucking Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 575, Folder 55)
  - Sub-Series 408-379. Wages
    - Goldsboro Union Station Company, Goldsboro, North Carolina. General, 1942-1955 (Box 575, Folder 56)
    - Goldsboro Union Station Company, Goldsboro, North Carolina. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 575, Folder 57)
    - Goldsboro Union Station Company, Goldsboro, North Carolina. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 575, Folder 58)
  - Sub-Series 408-380. Wages
    - Santa Fe Transportation Company. General, 1952-1958 (Box 576, Folder 1)
    - Santa Fe Transportation Company. General, 1948-1951 (Box 576, Folder 2)
    - Santa Fe Transportation Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 576, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 408-381. Wages
    - Detroit and Mackinac Railway Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement. Mediation Case No. A-7421, 1963-1965 (Box 576, Folder 4)
    - Detroit and Mackinac Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 576, Folder 5)
    - Detroit and Mackinac Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 576, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 408-383. Wages
    - Macon Terminal Company, Macon, Georgia. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 576, Folder 7)
    - Macon Terminal Company, Macon, Georgia. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 576, Folder 8)
    - Macon Terminal Company, Macon, Georgia. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 576, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 408-384. Wages
    - T.F. Quinn and Company. General, 1959 (Box 576, Folder 10)
    - T.F. Quinn and Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 576, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 408-385. Wages
    - Southeastern Demurrage and Storage Bureau. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 576, Folder 12)
    - Southeastern Demurrage and Storage Bureau. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 576, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 408-387. Wages
    - American Refrigerator Transit Company. General, 1947-1952 (Box 576, Folder 14)
    - American Refrigerator Transit Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 576, Folder 15)
    - American Refrigerator Transit Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 576, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 408-388. Wages
    - Burlington Refrigerator Express Company. General, 1944-1953 (Box 576, Folder 17)
    - Burlington Refrigerator Express Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 576, Folder 18)
    - Burlington Refrigerator Express Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 576, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 408-390. Wages
    - Philadelphia, Bethlehem and New England Railroad. General, 1943-1953 (Box 576, Folder 20)
    - Philadelphia, Bethlehem and New England Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 576, Folder 21)
    - Philadelphia, Bethlehem and New England Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 576, Folder 22)
    - Philadelphia, Bethlehem and New England Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 576, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 408-391. Wages
    - Chicago and Calumet River Railroad Company. General, 1944-1959 (Box 576, Folder 24)
    - Chicago and Calumet River Railroad Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 576, Folder 25)
    - Chicago and Calumet River Railroad Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 576, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 408-392. Wages
    - Greenwich and Johnsonville Railway. General, 1944-1954 (Box 576, Folder 27)
    - Greenwich and Johnsonville Railway. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 576, Folder 28)
    - Greenwich and Johnsonville Railway. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 576, Folder 29)
    - Greenwich and Johnsonville Railway. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 576, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 408-393. Wages
    - Texas City Terminal Railway Company, Texas City, Texas. General, 1943-1957 (Box 576, Folder 31)
    - Texas City Terminal Railway Company, Texas City, Texas. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 576, Folder 32)
    - Texas City Terminal Railway Company, Texas City, Texas. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 576, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 408-394. Wages
    - Savannah and Atlanta Railway. General, 1943-1953 (Box 576, Folder 34)
    - Savannah and Atlanta Railway. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 576, Folder 35)
    - Savannah and Atlanta Railway. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 576, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 408-395. Wages
    - Chicago Railroad Freight Collection Association. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 576, Folder 37)
    - Chicago Railroad Freight Collection Association. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 576, Folder 38)
    - Chicago Railroad Freight Collection Association. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 576, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 408-396. Wages
    - Wichita Terminal Association, Wichita, Kansas. General, 1945-1955 (Box 576, Folder 40)